Today is my day two to build a house worth Rs 1 crore through trading.
I never thought something like this would happen today.  I woke up in the morning and
saw that I had mistakenly
bought two lots of gold instead of one last night.
I was fully confident in my analysis
that the market would take a reversal and
I had made a downside entry in gold at night itself.
And this morning I woke up,
held the trade and went to my
plot.  When I went there I saw that the household
work was going on very fast.  And
all the labourers were working hard and doing
their work with dedication.
Then I come back to my setup and
see that I was making a good profit.
Then I book the profit.
This is my profit today.  So if you also want to
join me in this journey and
build your dream house and get A to
Z knowledge of trading, then follow me.